

Contact

Phone

+91 6290459905

Email

gobindasarkar909@gmail.com

Website

https://gobinda.theme-star.com

Address

Satkhira, Khulna ,Bangladesh

Education

2014 - 2018 University satkhira govt college

2012 - 2014

HSC

budhata b.b.m. collegiate school

2010 - 2012

SSC

budhata b.b.m. collegiate school

Language

English •

Hindi

...

Bangla • •

Gobinda Sarkar

Full Stack Web Developer Lead

Profile

Hi, I'm Gobinda Sarkar, I'm working as a professional Web developer and Designer. I've started my carrier in 2014 as a web designer. I also continued to keep learning and exploring new things for updating myself. I've made myself more efficient. I love to learn new things and working on them. I have 7 years' experience. Here are just a few things about me. I strive to provide excellent service in terms of quality of work, timely delivery, professional behavior, customer service, reliability, and dedication. I am a focused, skilled & efficient person. I specialize in building user and mobile-friendly websites using my wide range of skills in Frontend & Backend.

Experience

2020 - Present

zainiklab

Led Web Developer

The Lead Web Developer develops rich, interactive user experiences across the client's desktop and mobile platforms. The ideal candidate will have a passion for the

latest in HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript, work in a fast-paced and collaborative environment

2018 - 2020 zainiklab

Senior Web Developer

Senior web developers design, build, and optimize websites and other online applications. They are familiar with programming languages and SEO best practices, and often work with a team of junior web developers.

2014 - 2018

Front End Developer

Front-end web development, also known as client-side development is the practice of producing HTML, CSS and JavaScript for a website or Web Application

Skills

Html	•••	WordPress	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$
Css	••••	Ajax	\bullet \circ \circ
Javascript	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$	Myaql	ullet
Jquery	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$	Node Js	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
React Js	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$	Express Js	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
Php	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ$	Mongodb	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
Psd To Html	•••	Mongoos	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ$